I just have to
say claw hammers are the best
Hammers If you're not using a claw
hammer you
suck obviously that doesn't make any
sense and I'm just trying to make a
point real quick every time we keep
fighting about religions or or actually
frankly religion yes but tools and stuff
it's really all about the best tool for
the job you know you would never say to
somebody well I use I use you know ballp
Hammers and and that's the only hammers
I'm ever going to use so use the hammer
I said I said I said the ballp hammer
was the best yesterday now claw hammer
is the best right because I have new
information so let's not fight about
what Hammer is
best like seriously don't go into a
forum and declare that your Hammer is
better than everybody else's Hammer it's
really stupid it's stupid it doesn't
make any
sense imag just not using a claw hammer
if you're not using a claw hammer then
you must not know what you're doing you
know you should never have a job no one
should ever hire you I should fire you
for not using the right Hammer it's
totally stupid it's always been stupid
however and and coming in and telling
someone else that they should use a
hammer because of a specific reason some
when I'm programming I really want a
hammer
though we all do that's it that's all
this video is next time ask yourself
when you're arguing about an editor or
you're arguing about about a about a
programming language which is you know
or you're trying to ask here's another
one here's another one what's the best
Hammer I should learn which Hammer
should I learn how to use I get this
question all the time I get this
question constantly people come into my
chat and like Mr Rob I I I I really want
to learn how to use hammers which Hammer
should I
use you see where I'm going with this I
mean it's pretty obvious I'm kind of I'm
kind of hammering this to death oh my
God the jokes just keep
coming dad
jokes PHP is the best Hammer right so
you can't ask which Hammer is the best
and usually what what will I say back
I'll say I don't know what do you want
to
do what do you want to do with your
Hammer why do you want to use learn a
hammer maybe you need a saw what is it
you actually want to do tell me what you
want to do well I want to I want to get
a job using
[Laughter]
hammers okay let's see what are the jobs
you could use using hammers there's like
you could I mean you know construction
there's other thing you really don't
know what you want to
do uh I think the reactions are pretty
good too uh I think they've been pretty
they've been pretty open-minded the the
the Neo thing which is good because I
was really worried so so the you know
before you ask yourself the
question which Hammer should I learn ask
yourself the question
what do I want to do and if what you
want to do is do something that'll help
you you enjoy using Hammers and that's
totally fair I just really love using
hammers I love hammering stuff I love it
I absolutely do and some people do right
well what do you love hammering right
are you are you like you know do you
want to do a construction person you
want a sledgehammer you like really
breaking things up I I'm I'm taking this
to you know the nth level for a reason
because really that's what you're
ultimately asking and so the answer is
is inside yourself what do you want to
do do you want to break stuff up and
like a chain gang with a sledgehammer do
you want to you know do you do you want
to use your hammer and you want to put
crown molding in because you really like
amazing things like that is your Hammer
a part of another tool does it go with
another with like a like a and you're
like sculpture you're sculpting out of
it what is it that you want to do with
your hammer and then ask which Hammer is
best for that
job there that's all